Guide to the Jeffrey A. Diver papers,1965-1993.
Diver, Jeffrey A. papers, 1965-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jeffrey A. Diver papers, 1965-1993.
3084
Jeffrey A. Diver
.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, scrapbooks, manuscripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scrapbook of Jeffrey Arnold Diver, covering his years in R.O.T.C., the Vietnam War, and events leading to his becoming a conscientious objector; and Selective Service documents of Jeffrey Diver, Geoffrey A. Holmes and Howard Cornell in support of their applications for conscientious objector status. Also, handouts relating to Cornell Library acquisitions of gay and lesbian books and journals, 1980; letters about the New York State Task Force on Gay Issues, 1984; and correspondence relating to Cornell library card privileges for domestic partners.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Jeffrey Diver was a member of Cornell University Class of 1968.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Scrapbook of Jeffrey Arnold Diver, covering his years in R.O.T.C., the Vietnam War, and events leading to his becoming a conscientious objector; and Selective Service documents of Jeffrey Diver, Geoffrey A. Holmes and Howard Cornell in support of their applications for conscientious objector status. Also, handouts relating to Cornell Library acquisitions of gay and lesbian books and journals, 1980; letters about the New York State Task Force on Gay Issues, 1984; and correspondence relating to Cornell library card privileges for domestic partners. Files relating to Diver's employment in the Cornell University Library (CUL) system are also included.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Diver, Jeffrey A.; Cornell, Howard.; Diver, Jeffrey A.; Holmes, Geoffrey A.; United States--Armed Forces--Reserve Officer Training Corps.
Subjects:
Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975--Conscientious objectors.; Conscientious objectors.; Gay couples.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Howard Cornell conscientious objector materials (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Jeffrey Diver conscientious objector materials, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Geoffrey A. Holmes conscientious objector materials (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Domestic Partner records, 1980-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
- Scrapbook containing news clippings, selective service info., etc. (Box 1)
- CUGALA letter, from Art Leonard, March 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Open letter to CUL staff re: NYS gay rights legislation, 5/5/75 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- CUL employment files, March 1969-June 13 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- CUL employment files, June 14 1973-July 12 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- CUL employment files, July 15 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CUL employment files, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CUL employment files, 1982-May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- CUL employment files, June 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)